{
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7ois_Dupeyron",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "The_Officers'_Ward__film_",
    "human_readable": "Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron directed the film The Officers' Ward.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9158839583396912,
            "question": "Who directed the film The Officers' Ward?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8891478776931763,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8059556484222412,
            "question": "Is Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron a director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7407665848731995,
            "question": "Are there any actors who have starred in films directed by Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6920170187950134,
            "question": "Can you name another film directed by Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6303133368492126,
            "question": "What is the plot of The Officers' Ward about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6054708361625671,
            "question": "Where was The Officers' Ward filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5267950296401978,
            "question": "What year was The Officers' Ward released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3972330093383789,
            "question": "What genre is The Officers' Ward likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17240363359451294,
            "question": "Has Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron won any awards for his work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron directed the film The Officers' Ward.",
            "html": "yago_13692_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is The Officers' Ward likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_13692_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was The Officers' Ward released?",
            "html": "yago_13692_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was The Officers' Ward filmed?",
            "html": "yago_13692_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13692_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13692_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13692_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13692_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13692_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13692_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13692_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13692_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13692_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13692_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information that confirms Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron as the director of the film \"The Officers' Ward\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron directed the film \"La Chambre des officiers,\" which is also known as \"The Officers' Ward.\" Therefore, the statement \"Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron directed the film The Officers' Ward\" is correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}